http://www.vistek.ca/about/privacy

Helpful Customer Information for Holiday Shopping at Vistek
Also Click here for our Covid Update, Store Hours, Live Chat, Phone and Curbside Hours!
Vistek Ltd. - Privacy Policy
At Vistek Ltd., we are committed to providing our customers, with exceptional service. As providing this service involves the collection, use and disclosure of some personal information about our customers, protecting your personal information is one of our highest priorities. While we have always respected our customers' privacy and safeguarded their personal information, we have strengthened our commitment to protecting personal information.
This privacy policy has been developed to comply with Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act ("PIPEDA"). PIPEDA sets out rules for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in the course of commercial activity as defined in the Act.
Our Privacy Policy, in compliance with PIPEDA, outlines the principles and practices we follow in protecting customers' personal information. Our privacy commitment includes ensuring the accuracy, confidentiality, and security of our customers' personal information and allowing our customers to request access to, and correction of, their personal information.
Privacy Principles
All Vistek employees are responsible for maintaining and protecting all Personal Information under their control. Vistek has designated a Privacy Committee at their Head Office to oversee the company's compliance with PIPEDA and our Privacy Principles.
Privacy Committee
Vistek Ltd. Head Office
496 Queen Street East
Toronto, Ontario M5A4G8
privacy@vistek.ca
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of www.vistek.ca Www.vistek.ca collects some Personal Data from its Users. This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.
Policy summary
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Access to third-party accounts
Facebook account access Permissions: Access Requests
Twitter account access Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Analytics
Google Analytics Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Contacting the User
Contact form Personal Data: company name; email address; first name; last name; phone number; profession; province
Mailing list or newsletter Personal Data: email address; first name; last name
Phone contact Personal Data: phone number
Displaying content from external platforms
Google Fonts Personal Data: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Instagram widget and YouTube video widget Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Handling payments
PayPal Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Hosting and backend infrastructure
Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Microsoft Azure Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Interaction with external social networks and platforms
Twitter Tweet button and social widgets, Facebook Like button and social widgets and PayPal button and widgets Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Interaction with online survey platforms
SurveyMonkey Widget Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Managing contacts and sending messages
HubSpot Email Personal Data: email address; Usage Data
Mandrill Personal Data: various types of Data
Registration and authentication
Facebook Authentication, Google OAuth and Twitter OAuth Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Remarketing and behavioral targeting
Facebook Remarketing and Google Ads Remarketing Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Facebook Custom Audience Personal Data: Cookies; email address
SPAM protection
Google reCAPTCHA Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Tag Management
Google Tag Manager Personal Data: Usage Data
User database management
HubSpot CRM Personal Data: email address; phone number; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
HubSpot Lead Management Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Further information about Personal Data
Selling goods and services online The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery. The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by www.vistek.ca depends on the payment system used.
Contact information
Owner and Data Controller Vistek Ltd. 496 Queen Street East Toronto, Ontario, M5A 4G8 Owner contact email: privacy@vistek.ca
Full policy
Owner and Data Controller
Vistek Ltd. 496 Queen Street East Toronto, Ontario, M5A 4G8 Owner contact email: privacy@vistek.ca
Types of Data collected
Among the types of Personal Data that www.vistek.ca collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: first name; last name; phone number; company name; profession; province; email address; Cookies; Usage Data; various types of Data.
Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection.Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using www.vistek.ca.Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by www.vistek.ca is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for www.vistek.ca to provide its services. In cases where www.vistek.ca specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by www.vistek.ca or by the owners of third-party services used by www.vistek.ca serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the Cookie Policy, if available. Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through www.vistek.ca and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and place of processing the Data Methods of processing The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of www.vistek.ca (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time. Legal basis of processing The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:
Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law; provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject; processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner; processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.
In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Place The Data is processed at the Owner's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. Depending on the User's location, data transfers may involve transferring the User's Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data. Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data. If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section. Retention time Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for. Therefore:
Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed. Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.
The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority. Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.
The purposes of processing
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Service, comply with its legal obligations, respond to enforcement requests, protect its rights and interests (or those of its Users or third parties), detect any malicious or fraudulent activity, as well as the following: Contacting the User, Analytics, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Access to third-party accounts, Displaying content from external platforms, Handling payments, Hosting and backend infrastructure, Interaction with online survey platforms, Managing contacts and sending messages, Registration and authentication, Remarketing and behavioral targeting, SPAM protection, Tag Management and User database management.
For specific information about the Personal Data used for each purpose, the User may refer to the section “Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data”.
Facebook permissions asked by www.vistek.ca Www.vistek.ca may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User's Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it. This service allows www.vistek.ca to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc. For more information about the following permissions, refer to the Facebook permissions documentation and to the Facebook privacy policy. The permissions asked are the following: Basic information By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the User has made more of their Data public, more information will be available. Access Requests Provides read access to the User's friend requests.
Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Access to third-party accounts
This type of service allows www.vistek.ca to access Data from your account on a third-party service and perform actions with it. These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User. Facebook account access (Facebook, Inc.)
This service allows www.vistek.ca to connect with the User's account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook, Inc.
Permissions asked: Access Requests. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Twitter account access (Twitter, Inc.)
This service allows www.vistek.ca to connect with the User's account on the Twitter social network, provided by Twitter, Inc.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior. Google Analytics (Google Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of www.vistek.ca, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
Contacting the User
Contact form (www.vistek.ca)
By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes www.vistek.ca to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.
Personal Data processed: company name; email address; first name; last name; phone number; profession; province. Mailing list or newsletter (www.vistek.ca)
By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning www.vistek.ca. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to www.vistek.ca or after making a purchase.
Personal Data processed: email address; first name; last name. Phone contact (www.vistek.ca)
Users that provided their phone number might be contacted for commercial or promotional purposes related to www.vistek.ca, as well as for fulfilling support requests.
Personal Data processed: phone number.
Displaying content from external platforms
This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of www.vistek.ca and interact with them. This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows www.vistek.ca to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data processed: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)
Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows www.vistek.ca to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows www.vistek.ca to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Handling payments
Payment processing services enable www.vistek.ca to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, www.vistek.ca shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction. Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment. PayPal (PayPal Inc.)
PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – Privacy Policy.
Hosting and backend infrastructure
This type of service has the purpose of hosting Data and files that enable www.vistek.ca to run and be distributed as well as to provide a ready-made infrastructure to run specific features or parts of www.vistek.ca. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored. Amazon Web Services (AWS) (Amazon Web Services, Inc.)
Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a hosting and backend service provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: Canada – Privacy Policy.
Microsoft Azure (Microsoft Corporation)
Microsoft Azure is a hosting service provided by Microsoft Corporation.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: Canada – Privacy Policy.
Interaction with external social networks and platforms
This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of www.vistek.ca. The interaction and information obtained through www.vistek.ca are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network. This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. It is recommended to log out from the respective services in order to make sure that the processed data on www.vistek.ca isn’t being connected back to the User’s profile. Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
PayPal button and widgets (PayPal Inc.)
The PayPal button and widgets are services allowing interaction with the PayPal platform provided by PayPal Inc.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: See the PayPal privacy policy – Privacy Policy.
Interaction with online survey platforms
This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party online survey platforms directly from the pages of www.vistek.ca. If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. SurveyMonkey Widget (SurveyMonkey Inc.)
The SurveyMonkey Widget is a service for interacting with the SurveyMonkey online survey platform provided by SurveyMonkey Inc.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Managing contacts and sending messages
This type of service makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User. These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message. HubSpot Email (HubSpot, Inc.)
HubSpot Email is an email address management and message sending service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
Personal Data processed: email address; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Mandrill (The Rocket Science Group, LLC.)
Mandrill is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Registration and authentication
By registering or authenticating, Users allow www.vistek.ca to identify them and give them access to dedicated services. Depending on what is described below, third parties may provide registration and authentication services. In this case, www.vistek.ca will be able to access some Data, stored by these third-party services, for registration or identification purposes. Facebook Authentication (Facebook, Inc.)
Facebook Authentication is a registration and authentication service provided by Facebook, Inc. and is connected to the Facebook social network.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Google OAuth (Google Inc.)
Google OAuth is a registration and authentication service provided by Google Inc. and is connected to the Google network.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Twitter OAuth (Twitter, Inc.)
Twitter Oauth is a registration and authentication service provided by Twitter, Inc. and is connected to the Twitter social network.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Remarketing and behavioral targeting
This type of service allows www.vistek.ca and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of www.vistek.ca by the User. This activity is facilitated by tracking Usage Data and by using Trackers to collect information which is then transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity. Some services offer a remarketing option based on email address lists. In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services below, Users may opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. Users may also opt-out of certain advertising features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or ads settings in general. Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)
Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of www.vistek.ca with the Facebook advertising network.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
Google Ads Remarketing (Google LLC)
Google Ads Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Google LLC that connects the activity of www.vistek.ca with the Google Ads advertising network and the DoubleClick Cookie. Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies for ads personalization by visiting Google's Ads Settings.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
Facebook Custom Audience (Facebook, Inc.)
Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of www.vistek.ca with the Facebook advertising network.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; email address. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.
SPAM protection
This type of service analyzes the traffic of www.vistek.ca, potentially containing Users' Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM. Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)
Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc. The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google privacy policy and terms of use.
Personal Data processed: Cookies; Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Tag Management
This type of service helps the Owner to manage the tags or scripts needed on www.vistek.ca in a centralized fashion. This results in the Users' Data flowing through these services, potentially resulting in the retention of this Data. Google Tag Manager (Google LLC)
Google Tag Manager is a tag management service provided by Google LLC.
Personal Data processed: Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
User database management
This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to www.vistek.ca, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks' profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving www.vistek.ca. Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on www.vistek.ca. HubSpot CRM (HubSpot, Inc.)
HubSpot CRM is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
Personal Data processed: email address; phone number; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
HubSpot Lead Management (HubSpot, Inc.)
HubSpot Lead Management is a User database management service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Further information about Personal Data
Selling goods and services online
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery. The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by www.vistek.ca depends on the payment system used.
The rights of Users Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner. In particular, Users have the right to do the following:
Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data. Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below. Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing. Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected. Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner. Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User's consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof. Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.
Details about the right to object to processing Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection. Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.
How to exercise these rights Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.
Cookie Policy Www.vistek.ca uses Trackers. To learn more, the User may consult the Cookie Policy.
Additional information about Data collection and processing Legal action The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of www.vistek.ca or the related Services.The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities. Additional information about User's Personal Data In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, www.vistek.ca may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request. System logs and maintenance For operation and maintenance purposes, www.vistek.ca and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with www.vistek.ca (System logs) use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose. Information not contained in this policy More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document. How “Do Not Track” requests are handled Www.vistek.ca does not support “Do Not Track” requests.To determine whether any of the third-party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies. Changes to this privacy policy The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by notifying its Users on this page and possibly within www.vistek.ca and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.
Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.
Definitions and legal references
Personal Data (or Data) Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person. Usage Data Information collected automatically through www.vistek.ca (or third-party services employed in www.vistek.ca), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use www.vistek.ca, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment. User The individual using www.vistek.ca who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject. Data Subject The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers. Data Processor (or Data Supervisor) The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy. Data Controller (or Owner) The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of www.vistek.ca. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of www.vistek.ca. www.vistek.ca (or this Application) The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed. Service The service provided by www.vistek.ca as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/application. European Union (or EU) Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area. Cookie Cookies are Trackers consisting of small sets of data stored in the User's browser. Tracker Tracker indicates any technology - e.g Cookies, unique identifiers, web beacons, embedded scripts, e-tags and fingerprinting - that enables the tracking of Users, for example by accessing or storing information on the User’s device.
Legal information This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation). This privacy policy relates solely to www.vistek.ca, if not stated otherwise within this document.
Latest update: February 11, 2020
